<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
    <string name="Skyrim">"The next chapter in the Elder Scrolls saga arrives from the Bethesda Game Studios. Skyrim reimagines the open-world fantasy epic, bringing to life a complete virtual world open for you to explore any way you choose. Play any type of character you can imagine, and do whatever you want; the legendary freedom of choice, storytelling, and adventure of The Elder Scrolls is realized like never before. Skyrim's new game engine brings to life a complete virtual world with rolling clouds, rugged mountains, bustling cities, lush fields, and ancient dungeons. Choose from hundreds of weapons, spells, and abilities. The new character system allows you to play any way you want and define yourself through your actions. Battle ancient dragons like you've never seen. As Dragonborn, learn their secrets and harness their power for yourself."</string>

    <string name="MassEffect3"> BioWare completes the Mass Effect Trilogy with Mass Effect 3. Earth is burning. Striking from beyond known space, a race of terrifying machines have begun their destruction of the human race. As Commander Shepard, an Alliance Marine, the only hope for saving mankind is to rally the civilizations of the galaxy and launch one final mission to take back the Earth.</string>

    <string name="DarkSouls"> Dark Souls is a dark fantasy RPG designed to completely embrace the concepts of tension in dungeon exploration, fear in encountering enemies, the joy of new discoveries, and a high sense of achievement in progressing. The game is set in a dark fantasy world filled with decadent atmosphere, with a heavy emphasis on player freedom in discovering various tactics and strategies to use in weapon based combat.</string>

    <string name="Witcher3">You are Geralt, from the city of Rivia. All around you the towns and settlements of the Northern Kingdoms are being razed to the ground, as an otherworldly invading army known only as the Wild Hunt leaves a trail of blood-soaked destruction in its wake. As you prepare for a thunderous confrontation with the Wild Hunt, you’ll uncover a complex, gripping story and meet unforgettable characters. While exploring the Northern Kingdoms, you’ll discover that mysteries lurk inside every village, tree, and shadow.</string>

    <string name="DarkSoulsII"> Prepare to die... Again. Dare yourself to engage against intense gameplay in a vast world powered by a new engine. Immerse yourself into mind-bending environments filled with new twisted monsters and deadly bosses. A vast array of threats will prey on human senses and phobias - auditory hallucinations, vertigo, acrophobia, etc. More intricate customization options provide weapons and armor tailoring to player style.</string>

    <string name="Cyberpunk2077">Cyberpunk 2077 is an open-world, action-adventure story set in Night City, a megalopolis obsessed with power, glamour and body modification. You play as V, a mercenary outlaw going after a one-of-a-kind implant that is the key to immortality.</string>

    <string name="Fallout4">Bethesda Game Studios, the award-winning creators of Fallout 3 and Skyrim, welcomes you to the world of Fallout 4 . Winner of more than 50 Game of the Year awards, including top honors at the 2016 D.I.C.E. Awards. Fallout 4 is the studio’s most ambitious game ever and the next generation of open-world gaming. As the sole survivor of Vault 111, you enter a world destroyed by nuclear war. Only you can rebuild and determine the fate of the Wasteland. Welcome home.</string>

    <string name="TheOuterWorlds"> The Outer Worlds is a new single-player, sci-fi RPG from the developer of Pillars of Eternity and Fallout: New Vegas. Lost in transit while on a colonist ship bound for the furthest edges of the galaxy, you awake decades later to find yourself in the midst of a deep conspiracy threatening to destroy the far-flung Halcyon colony. Explore the furthest reaches of space and encounter various factions, all vying for power, and decide what kind of character you will become as your choices determine how the story unfolds. In the corporate equation for the colony, you are the unplanned variable.
</string>

    <string name="AssassinsCreedOdyssey">

Sentenced to death by your family, embark on a journey from outcast mercenary to legendary Greek hero and uncover the truth about your past.

Forge your path through a gorgeous world where mountains and sea collide. Meet Ancient Greece’s most famous figures and discover a pivotal point in history that shaped western civilisation.

For the first time in the series, choose the hero you want to become and decide the fate of the world around you.

Customize your equipment and master new special abilities, tailoring your character’s skillset to your play style. Fight your way across Greece, engaging in visceral battles both on land and sea, to become a legend.
</string>

    <string name="StardewValley">

You’ve inherited your grandfather’s old farm plot in Stardew Valley. Armed with hand-me-down tools and a few coins, you set out to begin your new life. Can you learn to live off the land and turn these overgrown fields into a thriving home? It won’t be easy. Ever since Joja Corporation came to town, the old ways of life have all but disappeared. The community center, once the town’s most vibrant hub of activity, now lies in shambles. But the valley seems full of opportunity. With a little dedication, you might just be the one to restore Stardew Valley to greatness!</string>

    <string name="GrandTheftAuto5"> Enter the lives of three very different criminals, Michael, Franklin and Trevor, as they risk everything in a series of daring and dangerous heists that could set them up for life.</string>

    <string name="Uncharted4">

Set three years after the events of Uncharted 3: Drake’s Deception, Nathan Drake has presumably left the world of fortune-hunting behind. However, it doesn’t take long for fate to come calling when Drake’s brother, Sam, resurfaces seeking his help to save his own life and offering an adventure Drake can’t resist.

On the hunt for Captain Henry Avery’s long-lost treasure, Sam and Drake set off to find Libertalia, the pirate utopia deep in the forests of Madagascar. Uncharted 4: A Thief’s End takes players on a journey around the globe, through jungle isles, far-flung cities and snow-capped peaks on the search for Avery’s fortune.
</string>

    <string name="GodofWar">

Kratos is a father again. As mentor and protector to Atreus, a son determined to earn his respect, he is forced to deal with and control the rage that has long defined him while out in a very dangerous world with his son.

His vengeance against the Gods of Olympus behind him, Kratos now lives in the realm of Norse deities and monsters.

It’s in this harsh, unforgiving world that he must fight to survive, and not only teach his son to do the same… but also prevent him from repeating the Ghost of Sparta’s bloodstained mistakes.

This staggering reimagining of God of War combines all the hallmarks of the iconic series – brutal combat, epic boss fights, and breathtaking scale – and fuses them with a powerful and moving narrative that re-establishes Kratos’ world.
</string>

    <string name="TombRaider">Tomb Raider explores the intense origin story of Lara Croft and her ascent from a young woman to a hardened survivor.</string>

    <string name="RedDeadRedemption2">

America, 1899. The end of the wild west era has begun as lawmen hunt down the last remaining outlaw gangs. Those who will not surrender or succumb are killed.

After a robbery goes badly wrong in the western town of Blackwater, Arthur Morgan and the Van der Linde gang are forced to flee. With federal agents and the best bounty hunters in the nation massing on their heels, the gang must rob, steal and fight their way across the rugged heartland of America in order to survive.

As deepening internal divisions threaten to tear the gang apart, Arthur must make a choice between his own ideals and loyalty to the gang who raised him.

From the creators of Grand Theft Auto V and Red Dead Redemption, Red Dead Redemption 2 is a sprawling tale of life in America at the dawn of the modern age.
</string>

    <string name="SpiderMan">"Sony Interactive Entertainment, Insomniac Games, and Marvel have teamed up to create an authentic Spider-Man adventure. This isn’t the Spider-Man you’ve met or ever seen before. This is an experienced Peter Parker who’s more masterful at fighting big crime in Marvel's New York. At the same time, he’s struggling to balance his chaotic personal life and career while the fate of millions of New Yorkers rest upon his shoulders."</string>

    <string name="BatmanArkhamCity">"Batman: Arkham City builds upon the intense, atmospheric foundation of Batman: Arkham Asylum, sending players flying through the expansive Arkham City - five times larger than the game world in Batman: Arkham Asylum - the new maximum security "home" for all of Gotham City's thugs, gangsters and insane criminal masterminds. Featuring an incredible Rogues Gallery of Gotham City's most dangerous criminals including Catwoman, The Joker, The Riddler, Two-Face, Harley Quinn, The Penguin, Mr. Freeze and many others, the game allows players to genuinely experience what it feels like to be The Dark Knight delivering justice on the streets of Gotham City."</string>

    <string name="ResidentEvilVillage">"Set a few years after the horrifying events in the critically acclaimed Resident Evil 7 biohazard, the all-new storyline begins with Ethan Winters and his wife Mia living peacefully in a new location, free from their past nightmares. Just as they are building their new life together, tragedy befalls them once again."</string>

    <string name="HorizonZeroDawn">"In an era where Machines roam the land and mankind is no longer the dominant species, a young hunter named Aloy embarks on a journey to discover her destiny.

In a lush, post-apocalyptic world where nature has reclaimed the ruins of a forgotten civilization, pockets of humanity live on in primitive hunter-gatherer tribes. Their dominion over the new wilderness has been usurped by the Machines – fearsome mechanical creatures of unknown origin."</string>

    <string name="StreetFighter5">"Experience the intensity of head-to-head battle with Street Fighter V! Choose from 16 iconic characters, each with their own personal story and unique training challenges, then battle against friends online or offline with a robust variety of match options.


Earn Fight Money in Ranked Matches, play for fun in Casual Matches or invite friends into a Battle Lounge and see who comes out on top! PlayStation®4 and PC players can also play against each other thanks to cross-play compatibility!"</string>

    <string name="Overwatch">"

Take part in an ever expanding universe of unforgettable characters, over-the-top weapons and powers and explosive multiplayer combat.

Bend time, defy physics and unleash a dizzying array of extraordinary abilities in a rapid-fire team-based shooter that has become a cult phenomenon.

Overwatch invites you to choose from a unique variety of heroes -  a time-jumping adventurer, a rocket hammer-wielding warrior or a transcendent robot monk, to name a few - and step into ever-expanding range of arenas to do battle in a unique 6-v-6 rumble.

Whether you're engaging in combat on the front line, providing defensive cover with your energy shield, or supporting your allies by amplifying their damage, every hero's abilities are designed to be effective as part of a team.

Get out there and protect the secrets of the mysterious Temple of Anubis, safely escort an EMP device through King's Row and more – the world of Overwatch is your battlefield.
"</string>

    <string name="ApexLegends">"

Jump into a hero shooter beyond battle-royale experience from Respawn Entertainment, the veteran studio behind the Titanfall series.

Apex Legends is a free-to-play, hero shooter with an ever expanding suite of finely-tuned legendary characters and powerful abilities filled with hundreds of cosmetic unlocks to hunt down.

Team up to battle for fame and fortune on the fringes of the Frontier - an all new region of the Titanfall universe - and master a roster of diverse characters, deep, tactical squad play, and a host of fresh innovations that seek to revolutionize the battle royale genre, from 60-person battle royale matches, 3v3 Arenas battles to limited-time modes and takeovers.
"</string>

    <string name="Destiny2">Dive into the world of Destiny 2 to explore the mysteries of the solar system and experience the definitive action MMO. Join millions of players, create your Guardian and start collecting unique weapons and armour to customize your look and play style. Embark on challenging co-op missions and a variety of competitive PvP modes. Experience Destiny 2’s evolving story with friends or explore the stars as a fireteam of one.</string>

    <string name="HalfLife2">"1998. HALF-LIFE sends a shock through the game industry with its combination of pounding action and continuous, immersive storytelling. Valve's debut title wins more than 50 game-of-the-year awards on its way to being named "Best PC Game Ever" by PC Gamer, and launches a franchise with more than eight million retail units sold worldwide.

NOW. By taking the suspense, challenge and visceral charge of the original, and adding startling new realism and responsiveness, Half-Life 2 opens the door to a world where the player's presence affects everything around them, from the physical environment to the behaviors even the emotions of both friends and enemies.

The player again picks up the crowbar of research scientist Gordon Freeman, who finds himself on an alien-infested Earth being picked to the bone, its resources depleted, its populace dwindling. Freeman is thrust into the unenviable role of rescuing the world from the wrong he unleashed back at Black Mesa. And a lot of people he cares about are counting on him."</string>

    <string name="Bioshock">"Explore the undersea city of Rapture, a haven for society's greatest minds that has devolved into a dystopian nightmare wrought by one man's hubris. Amidst the waterlogged ruins, a new ecosystem has emerged, where deranged Splicers hunt down the Little Sisters who would be helpless without their hulking Big Daddy guardians. Your only hopes for survival are quick thinking, reclaimed weaponry, and superhuman powers granted by DNA-altering Plasmids. To defeat Rapture's mutated monsters, you must become one."</string>

    <string name="Borderlands3">"

Return to the over-the-top world of Borderlands in this long-awaited addition to the acclaimed FPS series.

At the hard edge of the galaxy lies a group of planets ruthlessly exploited by militarized corporations, and brimming with loot and violence. This is your home - the Borderlands. Now, a crazed cult known as The Children of the Vault has emerged and is spreading like an interstellar plague. Only you have the allies and arsenal to take them down.

Play as one of four all-new, deeply customizable Vault Hunters - the ultimate treasure-seeking badasses of the Borderlands. Customize your Vault Hunter with tons of personalization options, and use their distinct skill trees to tailor abilities to your preferred playstyle.
"</string>

    <string name="DOOMEternal">"

Hell’s armies have invaded Earth. Become the Slayer in an epic single-player campaign to conquer demons across dimensions and stop the final destruction of humanity. The only thing they fear... is you.

Experience the ultimate combination of speed and power in DOOM Eternal - the next leap in push-forward, first-person combat.
"</string>

    <string name="FarCry5">"

Far Cry comes to America in the latest installment of the award-winning franchise.


Welcome to Hope County, Montana, land of the free and the brave but also home to a fanatical doomsday cult known as the Project at Eden’s Gate. Stand up to cult leader Joseph Seed, and his siblings, the Heralds, to spark the fires of resistance and liberate the besieged community."</string>

    <string name="CallOfDutyBlackOps2">"Pushing the boundaries of what fans have come to expect from the record-setting entertainment franchise, Call of Duty®: Black Ops II propels players into a near future, 21st Century Cold War, where technology and weapons have converged to create a new generation of warfare."</string>

    <string name="CallofDutyModernWarfare">"

Experience the global phenomenon. Immerse yourself in a raw and provocative new incarnation of the Modern Warfare series.

Developed by Infinity Ward, the original creator of the Modern Warfare series, this new iteration draws you into a visceral single-player story campaign that aims to push boundaries and break new ground for the franchise.

Engage in breathtaking covert operations alongside a diverse cast of international operatives and freedom fighters, skirmishing your way through iconic European landmarks and volatile Middle Eastern hot-zones.
"</string>

</resources>